Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 2
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 2
- Box: 43, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Item 8: Long Term Disability Income Continuance Plan, Publication (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Item 9: Report of the Members appointed by Government to the Task Force on Provincial Public Service Labour Relations, 1976; Publication (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Item 10: Your Pension Plan, Publication (Box 43, Folder 17)
    Author: Alberta. Employment Pensions Branch
  - Item 11: Your Pension Plan, Publication (Box 43, Folder 17)
- Box: 43, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Group: Postal Operations (supervisory), 1975; Publication (Box 43, Folder 18)
    Notes: contracts
  - Item 2: Group: Postal Operations (supervisory), 1970; Publication (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Postal Operations Group (non-supervisory), 1974; Publication (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Postal Operations Group (supervisory), 1968; Publication (Box 43, Folder 18)
- Box: 43, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Agreement between the Alberta Liquor Control Board and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees, 1977; Publication (Box 43, Folder 19)
    Author: Alberta Union of Provincial Employees
  - Item 2: Agreement between the Government of the Province of Alberta and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees representing Administrative Support Services (Division 1), 1976; Publication (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Agreement between the Government of the Province of Alberta and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees representing Administrative Support Services (Division 1), 1976; Publication (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: Agreement between the Government of the Province of Alberta and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees representing Educational Services (Division 8), 1976; Publication (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Item 5: Agreement between the Government of the Province of Alberta and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees representing Educational Services (Division 8), 1976; Publication (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Item 6: Agreement between the Government of the Province of Alberta and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees representing General and Field Support (Division 11), 1976; Publication (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Item 7: Agreement between the Government of the Province of Alberta and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees representing General and Field Support (Division 11), 1976; Publication (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Item 8: Agreement between the Government of the Provincw of Alberta and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees representing Health and Therapy Support Services (Division 9), 1976; Publication (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Item 9: Agreement between the Government of the Province of Alberta and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees representing Health and Therapy Support Services (Division 9), 1976; Publication (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Item 10: Agreement between the Government of the Province of Alberta and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees representing Institutional and Patient Support Services (Division 7), 1976; Publication (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Item 11: Agreement between the Government of the Province of Alberta and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees representing Medical and Rehabilitative Services (Division 10), 1976; Publication (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Item 12: Agreement between the Government of the Province of Alberta and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees representing Natural Resources Conservation Services (Division 5), 1976; Publication (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Item 13: Agreement between the Government of the Province of Alberta and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees representing Social Services Division (Division 6), 1976; Publication (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Item 14: Agreement between the Government of the Province of Alberta and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees representing Social Services Division (Division 6), 1976; Publication (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Item 15: Agreement between the Government of the Province of Alberta and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees representing Technical Services Bargaining Division (Division 12), 1976; Publication (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Item 16: Agreement between the Government of the Province of Alberta and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees representing Technical Services Bargaining Division (Division 12), 1976; Publication (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Item 17: Agreement between the Government of the Province of Alberta and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees representing Trades and Related Services (Division 4), 1976; Publication (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Item 18: Constitution of the Alberta Federation of Labour C.L.C., 1985; Publication (Box 43, Folder 19)
- Box: 43, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Agreement between the Government of the Province of Alberta and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees representing Correctional and Regulatory Services (Division 3), 1976; Publication (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Agreement between the Government of the Province of Alberta and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees representing Correctional and Regulatory Services (Division 3), 1976; Publication (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: Agreement between the Government of the Province of Alberta and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees representing Institutional and Patient Support Services (Division 7), 1976; Publication (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: Agreement between the Government of the Province of Alberta and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees representing Medical and Rehabilitative Services (Division 10), 1976; Publication (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Item 5: Agreement between the Government of the Province of Alberta and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees representing Natual Resources Conservation Services (Division 5), 1976; Publication (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Item 6: Agreement between the Government of the Province of Alberta and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees representing Trades and Related Services (Division 4), 1976; Publication (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Item 7: Agreement between the Alberta Liquor Control Board and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees, 1977; Publication (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Item 8: Agreement between the Government of the Province of Alberta and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees representing Administrative and Program Services (Division 2), 1976; Publication (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Item 9: Agreement between the Government of the Province of Alberta and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees representing Administrative and Program Services (Division 2), 1976; Publication (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Item 10: Master Agreement between the Government of the Province of Alberta and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees, 1976; Publication (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Item 11: Master Agreement between the Government of the Province of Alberta and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees, 1976; Publication (Box 43, Folder 20)
- Box: 43, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: This is who we arethe Federation: Voice of 230,000 British Columbians, Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
    Author: British Columbia Federation of Labour (C.L.C.)
  - Item 2: 17 Trade Unionists Jailed in One Year, Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: Bargaining in 1968 and 1969, Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
    Author: Paul Philips
  - Item 4: BCGEU Steward's Manual, Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Item 5: BCGEU Steward's Manual, Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Item 6: Grievance Manual for Stewards, Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Item 7: Grievance Manual for Stewards, Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Item 8: Guide for Employers: Regarding Employment Application Forms and Interviews Under the British Columbia Fair Employment Practices Act, Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Item 9: Guilty Until Proven Innocent: The Case Against the Use of Injunctions in Labour Disputes, Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Item 10: In the British Columbia Legislature, 1970; Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Item 11: Memorandum in Support of Proposed Legislation submitted by the British Columbia Federation of Labour to the Honourable W.A.C. Bennet, Premier and Members of the Provincial Cabinet, 1969; Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Item 12: Stamp Out Injunctions, Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
    Notes: bumper sticker
  - Item 13: Strike Manual, Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Item 14: Strike Manual, Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Item 15: Submission to the Select Standing Committee on Forestry and Fisheries of the Legislative Assembly of British Columbia by the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1969; Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Item 16: Appendix 1-7, Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Item 17: This is where we stand on public ownership, Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Item 18: This is where we standon pollution, Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Item 19: This is who we arethe Federation: Voice of 200,000 British Columbians, Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Item 20: This is who we arethe Federation: Voice of 200,000 British Columbians, Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Item 21: Unionism in British Columbia, Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Item 22: WCB News, 1980; Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
    Notes: v.23:no.6 (1980:Nov./Dec.)
  - Item 23: WCB News, 1981; Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
    Notes: v.24:no.1 (1981:Jan./Feb.)
  - Item 24: WCB News, 1981; Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
    Notes: v.24:no.2 (1981:Mar./Apr.)
- Box: 43, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: British Columbia Federation of Labour submission to the Honourable Ray G. Williston, Minister of Lands, Forests and Water Resources, 1969; Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: British Columbia Federation of Labour Submission to the Select Standing Committee of the Provincial Legislature on Mines and Railways in the matter of Surface Mining, 1969; Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: Submission by the British Columbia Federation of Labour to Pollution Control Board's Investigation of the Okanagan Valley, 1968; Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Item 4: B.C. Labour, 1970; Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
    Notes: April-May 1970.
  - Item 5: B.C. Labour, 1970; Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
    Notes: October 1970.
  - Item 6: Folder w/ various workshop papers - B.C. Federation of Labour, Canadian Labour Congress, Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Item 7: Folder w/ various workshop papers, newsletters - B.C. Federation of Labour, Canadian Labour Congress, Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Item 8: May we take a few minutes of your time to discuss our fellow citizensthe Indians, Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Item 9: The Labour Statesman, 1968; Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
    Notes: v.44:no.2 (1968:Feb.)
  - Item 10: Unions Are People, Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
- Box: 44, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Memorandum submitted by the British Columbia Federation of Labour to the Honourable W.A.C. Bennet, Premier and Members of the Provincial Cabinet, 1971; Publication (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Box: 44, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Constitution: British Columbia Federation of Labour, Canadian Labour Congress (amended as of June 1982), Publication (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Constitution: British Columbia Federation of Labour, Canadian Labour Congress (amended as of June 1982), Publication (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Constitution: British Columbia Federation of Labour, Canadian Labour Congress (amended as of June 1982), Publication (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Constitution: British Columbia Federation of Labour, Canadian Labour Congress (amended as of November 1976), Publication (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Constitution: British Columbia Federation of Labour, Canadian Labour Congress (amended as of November 1976), Publication (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Constitution: British Columbia Federation of Labour, Canadian Labour Congress (amended as of November 1979), 1982; Publication (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Constitution: British Columbia Federation of Labour, Canadian Labour Congress (amended as of November 1980), Publication (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Constitution: British Columbia Federation of Labour, Canadian Labour Congress (amended as of November 1980), Publication (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Constitution: British Columbia Federation of Labour, Canadian Labour Congress (amended as of November 1985), Publication (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Constitution: British Columbia Federation of Labour, Canadian Labour Congress (amended as of November 1986), Publication (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Constitution: British Columbia Federation of Labour, Canadian Labour Congress (amended as of November, 1980), Publication (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Labour Lobbying - A Practical Guide to Responsible Influence in Public Affairs, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Box: 44, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: I.C.B.C. the real dollars and sense story, 1975; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: I.C.B.C. the real dollars and sense story, Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: I.C.B.C. the real dollars and sense story, Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Notes: April 2nd, 1979.
  - Item 5: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Notes: April 30th, 1979.
  - Item 7: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Notes: April 4, 1979.
  - Item 9: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Notes: April 5, 1979.
  - Item 10: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1978; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Notes: December 15, 1978.
  - Item 12: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1978; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1978; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Notes: December 20th, 1978.
  - Item 14: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1978; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1980; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Notes: February 1st, 1980.
  - Item 16: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1980; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Notes: February 21st, 1979.
  - Item 18: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 19: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Notes: February 5th, 1979.
  - Item 20: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 21: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Notes: February 9, 1979.
  - Item 22: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 23: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Notes: January 18th, 1979.
  - Item 24: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 25: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Notes: July 19, 1979.
  - Item 26: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 27: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Notes: June 12, 1979.
  - Item 28: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 29: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Notes: June 14, 1979.
  - Item 30: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 31: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Notes: June 26, 1979.
  - Item 32: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Notes: June 6, 1979.
  - Item 33: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 34: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Notes: March 2nd, 1979.
  - Item 35: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 36: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Notes: May 18, 1979.
  - Item 37: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 38: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Notes: May 24, 1979.
  - Item 39: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1978; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Notes: November 9, 1978.
  - Item 40: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1978; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 41: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Notes: November 9, 1979.
  - Item 42: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 43: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1978; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Notes: October 13, 1978.
  - Item 44: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1978; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 45: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1978; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Notes: September 20, 1978.
  - Item 46: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1978; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 47: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1978; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Notes: September 25, 1978.
  - Item 48: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1978; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 49: Notes on Unions 1-8, Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 50: Oct. 14: Out to Fight Controls: Some questions and answers about Labour's National Day of Protest, 1976; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 51: Oct. 14: Out to Fight Controls: Some questions and answers about Labour's National Day of Protest, 1976; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Notes: Copy 2.
  - Item 52: Policy Statement: Defence Fund, 1975; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 53: Policy Statement: Hot Declaration, 1975; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 54: Policy Statement: Picketing, 1975; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 55: Prices, Profits, Cutbacks, Restraint, Unemployment, Wage Controls: What does it all mean to working British Columbians?, Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 56: Prices, Profits, Cutbacks, Restraint, Unemployment, Wage Controls: What does it all mean to working British Columbians?, Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 57: Prices, Profits, Cutbacks, Restraint, Unemployment, Wage Controls: What does it all mean to working British Columbians?, 1976; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 58: Provincial Finances: Setting B.C.'s Record Straight, Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 59: Provincial Finances: Setting B.C.'s Record Straight, Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 60: The employers campaign for "Right to Work" lawsA Passport to Poverty, 1976; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 61: The employers' campaign for "Right to Work" lawsA Passport to Poverty, 1976; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 62: The employers' campaign for "Right to Work" lawsA Passport to Poverty, 1976; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 63: Your Rights: a summary of the mimimum rights guaranteed to employees under British Columbia labour legislation, 1976; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 64: This is where we standagainst Racism, Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 65: This is where we standagainst Racism, Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 66: This is where we standon Boycotts, Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 67: This is who we arethe Federation: Voice of 200,000 British Columbians, Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 68: Wage Controls: Another attack on working people and their families, Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 69: Wage Controls: Another attack on working people and their families, Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 70: Wage Controls: Another attack on working peoples and their families, Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 71: Working PeopleLabourand the NDP, Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 72: Working PeopleLabourand the NDP, Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 73: Your Rights: A summary of the minimum rights guaranteed to employees under British Columbia labour legislation, 1976; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Box: 44, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Leaflets available from The Cooperative League of the USA, 1965; Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
    Author: The Cooperative League of the USA
  - Item 2: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1980; Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
    Notes: April 15, 1980.
  - Item 3: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1980; Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1980; Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
    Notes: April 3, 1980.
  - Item 5: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1980; Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1980; Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
    Notes: April 8th, 1980.
  - Item 7: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1980; Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1980; Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
    Notes: August 20, 1980.
  - Item 9: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1980; Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1980; Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
    Notes: August 22, 1980.
  - Item 11: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1980; Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
    Notes: February 14, 1980.
  - Item 12: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1980; Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1980; Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
    Notes: February 19, 1980.
  - Item 14: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1980; Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1979; Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1980; Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
    Notes: February 20, 1980.
  - Item 18: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1980; Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1980; Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
    Notes: February 27, 1980.
  - Item 20: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1980; Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Item 21: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1980; Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Item 22: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1980; Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Item 23: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1980; Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
    Notes: February 8, 1980.
  - Item 24: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1980; Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Item 25: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1980; Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
    Notes: January 18, 1980.
  - Item 26: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1980; Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Item 27: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1980; Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)